<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@android:color/white"
    tools:context=".Digital_intro">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="@android:color/white"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView5"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Digital image processing
\n In digital image processing, digital images are processed digitally, Photoshop is a good example, Instagram is another.
\n \n Image Processing has 2 major categories:
\n 1) Improvement of Pictorial information for human perception:
\n This category mainly concerns the operations on the pictures which are already stored in the system.
\n \n The applications are:-
\n (a) Image Enhancement: As I wrote above, the intensity of an image is a function of illumination. So sometimes due to low illumination conditions, we get a dull image. To overcome this we apply Image Enhancement techniques.
\n (b) Removing blurriness of Images: Many a time we observe that our images are blurred due to a problem with camera focus or when we take an image from a moving platform the images appear blurred. This can be overshadowed by Image restoration Techniques. It is also helpful in Noise Filtering.
\n (c) Segmentation: As the name suggests it helps to segment the part of the image on a predefined condition.
\n (d)  Morphological Processing: This is a very important aspect of Image Processing as deals with the shapes of the segmented image.
\n (e) Object Recognition, Representation and Description: These applications involve the recognition and representations of the image.
\n (e) Colour Image Processing: This application deals with the colours involved in the particular image, which is if we want to segment a red colour object from a particular image, then what conditions we need to provide.
\n \n 2. Image Processing for Robotics:
\n This category mainly concerns with the real-time applications of Image Processing. These applications are used in user-controlled robots, autonomous robots, autonomous machine application.
\n \n Some applications can be:
\n (a) Industrial Machine Vision for product assembly and inspection.
\n (b)Automated Target detection and tracking
\n (c)Finger Print, Iris, Facial Recognition Systems.
\n (d)Robotic Vision
\n (e)Autonomous robots and autonomous vehicles.
\n \n we saw an intro to the world of Image Processing and some of the major applications of Image Processing. Still, to perform all the above-said techniques, we would need a computing platform and a software. There are many soft wares which provide image processing applications in both the above categories, like, MATLAB, OpenCV, Image J, LABVIEW, to name a few.
"
            android:textColor="#00008B"
            android:textSize="18sp" />
    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>