<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@android:color/white"
    tools:context=".Introduction">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="@android:color/white"
        android:orientation="horizontal">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView6"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:background="@android:color/white"
            android:text="Image Processing: \n\n Sight/vision is one of the greatest powers of a human being. Our eyes can tell us the shape, size, colour of any and everything which comes in front of it.An Image is a 2 D light intensity function f(x,y). A digital image f(x,y) is discretized both in spatial coordinates and brightness. It can be considered as a matrix whose row, column indices specify a point in the image and the element value identifies the intensity value at that points. These elements are referred to as pixels. \n \n An intensity value stored at a pixel is defined as the product of illumination and reflectance at that particular point. You must have observed higher the illumination at a particular, the brighter image is.
\n Now the question in front of us is how to teach our bot this power of sight. As we know we can’t directly write codes for a bot to just see a thing and recognize it right away.
\n Image Processing, as its name suggests, is the processing of various algorithms to get the results according to our wish. A day to day life example of Image Processing can be of Adobe’s Photoshop or Microsoft’s Picture Manager or Google’s Picasa are a few software. These software’s provide a user interface for the user to apply different applications such as cropping, colour changing. Although these applications are easy to use the software behind it has been written by a certain code.
\n In this course we are going to discuss the basic usage of Image processing with respect to robotics and their further applications.
\n \n There are two types of image processing;
\n 1.	Analog
\n 2.	Digital
"
            android:textColor="#00008B"
            android:textSize="18sp" />
    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>